<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Snake Eyes Gaming Club Open League feed</title>
    <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Blood bowl league RSS feed</description>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 22:14:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>OBBLM 0.97 SVN</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Big Fist Bashers (1) vs. The Treacle Mine Pickers (1)</title>
      <description>First Half.&#xD;
Snotling Kneewizzle grabbed the ball and ran toward the dwarfs, managing to fall over after going for it.&#xD;
Dwarfs then managed to grab the ball and Casanunda managed a throw to Modo.&#xD;
Modo run down the wing to linger by the touchline as central brawl continued, TD on turn 7 followed by a one turn fight.&#xD;
&#xD;
Second Half&#xD;
Casanunda passed the ball to Madam Sharn&#xD;
Madam Sharn made a run up field.&#xD;
Thrigg'mund Gah attempting a break tackle into 2 Touch Zones in attempt to catch Madam Sharn, first roll 2 and re roll 1 = stunned himself.&#xD;
Madam Sharn then blitz on snotling Kneewizzle, Tripple push into re-roll of triple skulls.&#xD;
Greedchart then managed to take the ball before scoring a TD.&#xD;
Greedchart later smashed up badly on the proceeding line up.&#xD;
Last minute attempt by BFB with a snotling throw into a Dwarf who then landed and managed to fumble picking up the ball ending the half.&#xD;
Manbead gifted to the TMP at end of match.</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 19:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1532891941</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: The Treacle Mine Pickers (0) vs. The Ru-volting Bad Drags (3)</title>
      <description>In this the second round of the Chiswick Open, The Ru-Volting Bad Drags shambled their way to Sticky Fields for a rematch against the Treacle Mine Pickers.&#xD;
&#xD;
Weather was ideal and the pus was warm as the players took to the field, Nurgle warrior Thorgy sores was pouting on the sideline following her injury last match however Bianca del Rotto kept her entertained by throwing some heavy shade at the opposing team from the dugout throughout most of the match.&#xD;
&#xD;
At kick off the dwarf team saw to it that they would have every advantage this game by promptly, and thoroughly accidentally, trampling the referee as they advanced giving both sides an opportunity to take cheap shots at each other for the remainder of the match.&#xD;
&#xD;
The dwarves started strong after receiving the ball with a string of heavy knockdowns and runner Casanunda keeping a tight grip on the ball as he made his way through the front lines. Mid way through the half he made a sprint for the opposing touchline and was quickly surrounded by the Bad Drags pestigors who had been lurking in defence. In a brash attempt at some elf like agility, he quickly found himself face down in the dirt and knocked unsconcious after trying to dodge around the slobbering beasts. Putrice royale was quick to capitalise on the mistake scooping up the ball easily with her suspicious looking 5th limb and made a dash for the Pickers half. With much jostling and shoving, Putrice managed to force her way through the Dawi defences to score a touchdown as the half time horn was blown.&#xD;
&#xD;
Due to the bloody minded efforts of the Dwarves, and the absence of a conscious referee, Grabpot Thundergust was allowed to enter the field for the second half and was very much ready to bust some rotten skulls.&#xD;
&#xD;
Receiving the ball, the nurgle team put up a strong wall of blubbery defence at the line of scrimmage, with Retox bolstering the middle of the field in a flurry of tentacles. Again, wise pushing and some effective blocks sending a couple of dwarves to the sidelines saw Putrice Royale AGAIN making headway in to dwarf territory clutching the ball. She managed to burst free from a clutch of Dwarven defenders like a zit to streak down the sidelines for another touchdown just before the 3rd quarter.&#xD;
&#xD;
A stunning kick off from the Nurgle team saw the ball end up dangerously close to the line of scrimmage and perfectly positioned for a steal, which is exactly what happened. Lacking a competent runner, blitzer Modo attempted to take on the mantle with uncharacteristic speed for one so heavily armoured and made his way towards the front line. He was however quickly swallowed up by the foetid and fly filled defensive line and the ball was quickly squeezed free.&#xD;
&#xD;
This time it was Katya who scooped up the ball and ran in for a late game (and entirely uncommon) 3rd touchdown for the nurgle team.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
For her absolutely well deserved efforts, Putrice Royale was given the MVP award for the Bad-Drags, whilst Carrot Ironfoundersson took the nod for the dwarves for the 3rd time this season. Many of his teammates are beginning to think there is some excessive rigging going on with the crowd voting for the MVP awards this season as Carrot has barely got his toes dirty each game. Investigations are ongoing as to who needs bribing further to even the playing fields.</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 21:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1531950603</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: You're A Lizard, Harry! (0) vs. Big Fist Bashers (1)</title>
      <description>Turn 1 USB sent off for a foul on Dumbledore. YAWH managed to hold the line after dropping the ball, BFB got ball but YAWH great blitz resulting in a knocked down ogre scattering the ball with 2 turns to go.&#xD;
&#xD;
Second half snotling got ball, scrum, handoff ran down left flank, with saurus KO everywhere. Sking break for a dodge blitz only to fall over on going for it roll.</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 00:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1530922584</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: The Treacle Mine Pickers (1) vs. Going for Ghould (0)</title>
      <description>Week 6 of the Chiswick open saw the treacle mine pickers make the treachourous journey to the misty peaks of Cripple Peak in the Broken Tooth Mountains to play on the surprising lush fields of Going for Gould's home turf.&#xD;
&#xD;
The gate was high and the air was thin, both teams and the fans were out for blood...&#xD;
&#xD;
The dwarves received for the first half, with Grabpot Thundergust going deep in the paint facing off against both of the Ghould's mummies at kick off. This wasn't to be the most foolish of plays as from that point on, Madam Ocelot couldn't seem to find her ankles. What was foolish however was Casanunda attempting some uncharacteristic Dawi flair and muffing a pass to his running mate cheery immediately after kick off. Seeing an opportunity to close the gap, the shambling undead attempted to break through the front line of dwarven muscle, but to no avail. Through concentrated effort the dwarves pushed back the horde of zombies and managed a mid half touchdown, Cheery Littlebottom running in the touchdown in spectacular fashion.&#xD;
&#xD;
After the first drive neither team had taken many casualties, with the only removal on the Ghould's side coming after the Spleenfondler tripped over his own arm.&#xD;
&#xD;
In an entertaining piece of sideline theatre, the Pickers head coach drunkenly attempted to argue with the referees that a 9 foot tall steam powered engine of death was a perfectly legal member of the team and should be allowed to remain on the field. After repeatedly burping in the head referees face and falling limply on his shoulder sobbing he was gently removed from the sidelines by his coaching staff for a lie down.&#xD;
&#xD;
The remainer of the half proceeded with the Ghould's recieving the ball and attempting again to break through the dwarf defences, after much pushing and shoving (and a blatant foul from Rhys Rhysson) the whistle blew for half time.&#xD;
&#xD;
Down 2 players the dwarves needed to put in a huge effort to stop the undead team from easily scoring in the second half, and true to form they dug in their steel shod heels and put in the effort of a lifetime. Fortunately the undead team were down to a single mummy after a well placed punch left the other spinning in the dugout, moaning more than is usual for one in their condition.&#xD;
&#xD;
It's uncertain whether the Ghoulds were scared or excited during the second half, but they certainly took to the task with great energy. There were bodies flying from both teams and the stretcher bearers were rarely still. The most spectacular moment of the half came in the last quarter of the game where no less than 3 players were measured for a coffin, new ones in the case of the undead team. &#xD;
&#xD;
Both dwarf star runner Cheery Littlebottom and the Gravetickler were torn apart by the baying undead crowd and Wight blocker Withers was slaughtered by the blades fist of Madam Sharn in a fit of rage fuelled vengeance after seeing her only other female teammate in a bloody heap on the sidelines.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
The game ended with only 3 of the undead team on the field as the final whistle blew and the teams necromancer greedlily rubbing his palms together as his coaching team stole away the remaining body parts of the dwarf runner.&#xD;
&#xD;
A sombre victory for the Dwarves but one that they will remember for years to come as they finally broke the winning streak of the Ghoulds.</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 22:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1530310822</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Going for Ghould (2) vs. Big Fist Bashers (0)</title>
      <description>A slow and gruelling scrum with two halves saw very little injuries, only two incidents registered at the end of the mach causing Big Fist Bashers, Mhorg Thrag'u to miss the next game. Withers the ghoul appeard to leave the pitch in bits only to come on minutes later looking fresh and regenerated.&#xD;
Two touchdowns in as many halves by Going for Ghould saw both Ghouls, Gravetickler and Spleenfondler add to their deathtime records.&#xD;
Due to circumstances beyond their control, with much much much relief to the Big Fist Bashers who were seriously lacking in pitch based snotlings, the game ended after Going for Ghould's second try on turn 15, with both teams leaving the stadium just before lockdown.&#xD;
A pitiful display by the Ogres saw them lose fans, quite literally, only for them to be resurrected to join the ranks Going for Ghould fan-base!</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 12:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1529151207</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: The Treacle Mine Pickers (2) vs. You're A Lizard, Harry! (1)</title>
      <description>Last night saw a late entry in to the Snake Eyes League with 'You're a Lizard Harry' coming to Sticky fields to face the Treacle Mine Pickers. The Harry's could not field a full team until part way through the season as they were waiting for their head coach to escape from a petting zoo run by Wulfrik the Wanderer in Norsca.&#xD;
&#xD;
It was a glorious sunny day at the fields and the groundsmen had managed to get a lovely shine on the pitch, the gate was high and the Pickers home crowd was ready for a proper display of Dawi violence. It has been several weeks since the pasting they received at the hand of the RuPaul Bad Drags [game records redacted for decency reasons] and there were still several players on their roster either picking pus out of their ears or recovering from unfortunate tentacle wounds.&#xD;
&#xD;
There was a thunderous applause as the Deathroller pilot Grabpot Thundergust took to the field for the first time this season, lining up against the Kroxigor Dumblegore the crowd knew they were in for a treat.&#xD;
&#xD;
The game started with the Harry's receiving the ball and making swift progress towards the dwarven lines, the trauma of their last game against the nurgle team was clearly still on their minds as the blocks and tackles placed against the lizards were limp at best.&#xD;
&#xD;
Within seconds Jon the skink had successfully snuck the ball past 2 of the pickers defenders and in to the end zone, his pre-game ritual of bathing in lavender scented parrafin oil paying dividends!&#xD;
&#xD;
After just a short display of strength and martial prowess Thundergust was promptly ejected from the game by the officials.&#xD;
&#xD;
The return kick-off was intercepted by a blitz from the Harry's front line with Jon again slipping himself through the line of scrimmage and under the ball in a flash! However his possession was short lived, as he came down do earth Casanunda connected a perfect right hook which dislodged the ball and sent it in to the press of bodies on the front line. With gutter runner like speed, agility and swiftness Casanunda ran in a touchdown just before the close of the half.&#xD;
&#xD;
Tactical application of a beer barrel at half time helped several of the lizards back to the field and invigorated the dwarves to double down on their performance.&#xD;
&#xD;
Fielding the ball again at the start of the second half Casanunda started his run up the field with a solid bodyguard of linemen, progress was good until their cage was smashed apart by the rampaging Dumblegore at the half way line. Blows were traded in lizard territory for the entirety of the half before the ball finally burst out by the endzone to be picked up by Madam Sharn to be run in for a late second dwarf touchdown!&#xD;
&#xD;
The ensuing pandemonium from the stands caused the referees to totally lose track of time giving the lizardmen a final chance to return the ball for a draw. The dwarves stacked their back line in defence however it wasn't needed, the lizardmen resigned themselves to bloody revenge at the line of scrimmage, the pile of bodies finally being cleared 5 minutes after the final whistle blew.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
With a second win of the league under their (substantial) belts, the dwarves vigour was clearly improved. Bugmans brewery had to pull their sponsorship of the Pickers just 3 hours after the game for fear of taking a loss due to the team and coaching staff celebrations.&#xD;
&#xD;
The only major injuries of the game came from Don the skink tripping over his own frill and badly dislocating his thumb and Saurus blocker Barry receiving a smashed ankle.</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 09:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1529140992</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: The Treacle Mine Pickers (0) vs. The Ru-volting Bad Drags (2)</title>
      <description>++::RECORDING DELETED BY REQUEST OF NUFFLE DECENCY COMMITTEE::++&#xD;
&#xD;
This week any viewers hoping to catch the recording of this game on Cabal Vision will be sore-ly disappointed.&#xD;
&#xD;
Due to the disturbing and gory display of violence and debauchery on the pitch, the regulatory committee for decency (such as there is any in this sport) has deemed any and all recordings, images, brass rubbings, souvenirs, signatures, merchandise and any physical memorabilia of the event be destroyed to save future generations from having to experience that level of horror outside of a pitched battle. &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
The ultimate outcome was a resounding victory for the Nurgle team, after their first 3 matches they entered the pitch in a frothing, oozing line of pure chaos enhanced hatred. The Dwarven team were just unfortunate enough to be on the other side of the line from them.&#xD;
&#xD;
Before there was even time to note the names of the new journeymen players for the Pickers, one was already dead in a heap on the ground, and several others were fighting for their lives rolling on the ground choking on flies and trying to pull nurglings out of their beards.  The level of pus-based violence witnessed over the first 30 minutes of play was astounding, with nearly half the dwarf team on the sidelines without any response from the now severely diminished dwarf players.&#xD;
&#xD;
From the flying strings of slobber and maggots Chi-Chi de Mange was able to break through for an end of half touchdown, giving the dwarves a few moments to compose themselves with a stiff drink before taking to the field again. By the end of the first half only 7 dwarves were left standing on the pitch...&#xD;
&#xD;
The second half saw much of the same, more dwarves were knocked out and injured whilst the Nurgle team seemed invulnerable to all attack. One moment of respite came when Thorgy Sores tripped on her ritual violin bow and managed to snap her ankle on the way down to the turn, beyond that the Dwarf team kept on punching only to find their fists hitting snapping maws or clusters of blubbery warts.&#xD;
&#xD;
Putrice Royale ran in a second TD for the Chaos team sealing the dwarves fate, a short down after the score saw the dwarves finally limp off for a well deserved keg of beer and 8 baths each. The Nurgle team, resplendent in their victory performed a lap of honour around their home field (The Work-Room) which (considering the lewd use of tentacles and additional mutated mouths) only added to the disturbing scenes that day.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Putrice Royale was a well deserved MVP for the Nurgle team and Albrecht Albrechtsson was only given the nod by the dwarven coach as he was the least filthy player able to speak at the end of the match.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Reports following the match tell us that the dwdarf journeyman pounded flat by the beast of Nurgle was seen dragging its bloated corpse back towards the Nurgle dressing room at the end of the match and the Dwarf coaching staff had been in hurried negotiations with famed Death Roller pilot Grabpot Thundergust to hire his services for the rest of the season. Clearly the need for more stopping power was weighing heavily in their minds!&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 09:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1525080761</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: The Treacle Mine Pickers (0) vs. Big Fist Bashers (1)</title>
      <description>As the heavens opened and the Ogres started looking upwards wondering what was going on, the snotlings struggled to gain the attention of their larger compadres! Due to the delay, the rain and the packed stadium, the Fans started rioting.&#xD;
&#xD;
Having the home advantage, the dwarfs fans managed to stun a three out of the five Ogres and a few of the little green things! During all the confusion, one of the Dwarf superfans, wearing all the team attire, remained on the pitch for the start of the first half!&#xD;
&#xD;
As the The Pickers Kicked-off, a full on brawl immediately erupted!&#xD;
B'hrain Bloodaxe, dauntless as ever made some fearless blocks against his larger foes and was quickly put in his place only to spend the rest of the game recovering in the dugout.&#xD;
&#xD;
While the brawl progressed further, the dwarfs did what they do best and systematically surrounded the Bashers - Ogre by Ogre keeping them under control. As the brawl continued, the new Snotling player USB managed not only to pick up the ball and keep it under control, but actually managed to find a route down the sidelines.&#xD;
&#xD;
The dwarfs made a stunning effort to respond slowing the Snotling advance down allowing for the brawl to slowly shift position as both Dwarfs and Ogres punched and jostled with each other to get loser to the ball carrier. &#xD;
&#xD;
Slipping through the legs of Mhorg Thrag'u, as the Ogre was pushed into the crowd, the snotling advanced cautiously using his team mates as a meat wall.&#xD;
&#xD;
As the final minutes of the first half drew to a close a few of the dwarfs made a break for the ball without success allowing the snotling to breeze over the end-line. A quick setup allowed the Pickers a quick drive that saw some additional damage reign down on the Bashers.&#xD;
&#xD;
The second half saw the Bashers kicking off. As the ball was kicked high, the Ogres manged a sneaky manoeuvre to gain maximum bashing effect for a perfect defence! As the ball thudded to the ground, the Dwarf runners surrounded the slippery leather pigskin while their fellow teammates took a tremendous beating by an endless line of Ogres during which, the superfan was spotted by Jim Kemmukush who went to town giving the nameless Dwarf a Serious Concussion.&#xD;
&#xD;
The half progressed with a scrum for the ball, that seemed to exchange hands frequently due to the added slippery effect of the continuing driving rain. As the snotlings threw fouls left right and center, the Pickers slowly squashed them under their feet leaving only a tight Fancy (Collective Noun) of Ogres left.&#xD;
&#xD;
As the ball teetered on the sidelines, Skulgrug Red Gloves took the decision to attempt to handle the ball only to be pushed into the crowd. The attrition continued on both sides and as the beers were prepared on the sidelines players from both teams collapsed into a tired, bruised and breathless pile on the ground.</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 23:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1523663654</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: The Deadworld Oligarchy (0) vs. Big Fist Bashers (0)</title>
      <description>As the crowd rolled up, the skies were blue and the sun was shining for week 4 of the Chiswick Open.&#xD;
A great turn out of 25,000 fans saw a 3:2 ratio in The Big Fist Bashers favour.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Deadworld Oligarchy kicked off the first half that saw the Big Fist Bashers brilliant coaching lead to a rather needed additional re-roll.&#xD;
The ball was kicked deep into The Bashers half leaving some time for The Oligarchy to make their advance. By some miracle, a Snotling managed to pickup the ball and move up-field on the ledt hand side only to be confronted by a pile of confused Ogres and Bumbling Zombies.&#xD;
&#xD;
As the brawl continued, injuries were suffered on both sides that saw Moneybit the Snotling suffer a Broken Jaw at the hands of Zombie, Kinky Friedman. Judge Lawless the Werewolf then bit hard into Kneewizzle's Arm causing a fracture. Butch Otter, the Flesh Golem, got set upon and also suffered a Broken Arm from Ogre Skulgrug Red Gloves while Tim Shotwells neck was broken by Thrigg'mund only to magically snap back into place as Tim was being carried off the pitch.&#xD;
&#xD;
Towards the very end of the half, the ball carrying Snotling emerged from the flesh heap only to trip up and fumble the ball. The crowd was left stunned as the whistle was blown.&#xD;
&#xD;
The second half saw The Bashers kicking off and the ability of The Deadworld Oligarchy to shake of KO's was relentless. As the ball was kicked, the fans rushed the pitch and stunned The Oligarchies Kinky Friedman, Andress Twinkle and a nameless journeyman. With more fans, The Bashers got off lightly with Jim and Farsnap going down. Some spectators swore they saw fans of The Bashers beating some sense into #2, Jim Kemmukush, due to his continuing ineptitude at remembering what to do.&#xD;
&#xD;
As the crowd tired and retook their seats, The Bashers formed a meat wall against a refreshed Judge Lawless who was looking for a way through.&#xD;
Both of The Oligarchies Wights made a break for the end-zone with one of them meeting the fist of Mhorg Thrag'u seriously limiting The Oligarchies options. &#xD;
&#xD;
After a bit of positioning and a few scuffles, Lawless made a break down the right side and punched through a smaller section of the wall, as his thirst for Snotling blood took hold, Lawless followed his target around the sidelines. In swarming fashion the Snotlings managed to surround Lawless to put a stop to the pending touchdown. All the while, The while the Ogres were tied up swatting away zombies. Eventually the Snotlings let the crowd do the work as they just managed to push Lawless off the pitch, much to the relief of the Bashers fans.&#xD;
&#xD;
A few more non-eventful scuffles saw Snotlings flying all over the place, murmurs in the crowd suggested that wizards were providing some kind of force fields for the little green things. As the clock ran out and with no hope of a touchdown, Roughcrook managed a showboating dodge, dodge, pickup, dodge and throw that was readily caught by a fellow team member.&#xD;
&#xD;
Judge Lawless of The Deadworld Oligarchy gained MVP due to his durability in the first half and sheer audacity in the second half. Lawless also came away with a new found skill at Blocking from his time in the crowd.&#xD;
For his improvement at remembering, Jim Kemmukush was awarded MVP for The Big Fist Bashers and Skulgrug Red Gloves picked up a knack for Guarding his team mates.&#xD;
&#xD;
It was certainly a game with few plays and many punches but the Journeyman referred to be the crowd as "Leg Man" impressed The Deadworld Oligarchy's coach so much by the end of the match, he was hired on the spot.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 23:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1523055984</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: The Ru-volting Bad Drags (0) vs. Big Fist Bashers (0)</title>
      <description>With a large team value difference the Big Fist Bashers took advantage of some pre-match training and a Bloodweiser Babe/Barrel to hype themselves up for the big match.&#xD;
&#xD;
Just before kickoff clouds gathered and rain began to pour making the pickup and passing game somewhat of a chore.&#xD;
&#xD;
The first half saw a brutal mid-pitch brawl with several snotlings doing what they do best, fouling and hurting. Unbelievably during the scuffle one ogre got badly hurt and two more were knocked out leaving the other Ogres pondering what to do next while more snotlings crumbled. The Bad Drags came out relatively better off with just a few KO's.&#xD;
&#xD;
A big break from the Ru-volting Bad Drags towards the end of the half saw a Chi Chi De Mange make a break for the touchline. As the Nurgle crowd started cheering and farting a bad attempt at a block caused a double down leading to a turnover just before Chi Chi reached the endzone.&#xD;
&#xD;
The second half saw a Ogre regain his brain and enter the frey once more. A rather thin setup from the Bashers managed to  receive the kickoff and hold the ball in the ever popular snotling cage until the snotling holding the ball was pushed into the crowd. As the ball was thrown back in by the crowd, both teams looked exhausted as the whistle was blown.&#xD;
&#xD;
Amazingly no deaths or serious injuries were recorded and the crowd left recounting blow by blow accounts of what they could recall from the endless brawl they just witnessed. Some Nurgle fans we heard to be cursing Chi Chi's attempt at a try leading them to seek out other teams to follow.&#xD;
</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 22:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1522965721</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: The Treacle Mine Pickers (1) vs. The Deadworld Oligarchy (0)</title>
      <description>Week 3 of the Chiswick Open saw the Treacle Mine Pickers play at home (Sticky Fields) against the Deadworld Oligarchy!&#xD;
&#xD;
Played in ideal conditions, this game was a veritable bloodbath. &#xD;
&#xD;
The kick off saw the Dwarves receive the ball and start the game in brutal style, within minutes there were already several opposing players on the bench courtesy of the dwarven front line.  After his first game of the season Magnus Magnusson has become a powerhouse in the mid-field, fighting off opponents left right and centre whilst still having the energy to help his teammates.&#xD;
&#xD;
Soon after picking up the ball, runner Casanunda found himself in the path of a slathering warewolf who had broken through the line of scrimmage in black brutal fashion. Quick thinking and quick hands managed to get the ball to Cheery Littlebottom and she swifly made a break for the sidelines.&#xD;
&#xD;
This however was where things started to go wrong for the home team. Within moments of getting behind a protective screen of players Cherry found herself easily outnumbered after 3 of her teammates were launched into the stands by charging wights and golems. It worked out fairly well however as the dwarves were caught by their cheering kinsman and each crowd surfed safely back to the dugout.&#xD;
&#xD;
The ball was recovered well by Judge  Lawless and with a howl he made a break for the miners end zone. In a desperate move, Madam Sharn broke away from the front line to tackle the lycan single handedly dangerously close to her lines. She managed to ankle tap the beast saving a late half touchdown.&#xD;
&#xD;
After the dust settled from the first half the Oligarchy had just 9 players to bring back to the field, a grim tally taken by the dwarven blockers whilst they were still at full strength.&#xD;
&#xD;
With a high kick sent to the necromantic lines in turn 2 the shambling horde seemed set to make a run down the field. Again Judge Lawless took up the ball in his fangs and started bounding down the pitch, only to be met by a wall of purple and white. Doubling back he ran to the safety of his own half to weigh up his options. With rotting bodies flying in all directions at the line of scrimmage he made a break down one half of the field, attempting to claw one of the dwarf runners to death on the way. He was eventually brought low by none other than number 5 Rhys Rhysson, leaving the ball on the ground for Cheery Littlebottom to scoop up and sprint to the end zone. It took an unexpected level of dwarven agility and all the distance her stout legs had in them to get her there, but with a final dive she cleared the line in spectacular fashion.&#xD;
&#xD;
The late score saw the game close at a hard fought 1-0 to the home team. The gate at this game was huge so both teams should expect a hefty pay out from the sponsors.&#xD;
&#xD;
For his heroics in tackling the enemy flesh golems to the ground all game, B'hrain Bloodaxe was awarded the MVP for the dwarven team.&#xD;
&#xD;
We are hearing reports that Ben Bushyhead of the Oligarchy will be missing next game with a significant injury, but their necromancer is confident he will be seen lurking around the back field again before long.</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 22:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1522879226</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Going for Ghould (2) vs. The Ru-volting Bad Drags (0)</title>
      <description>The Ru-volting Bad Drags got off ton arguably great start with BenDeLaPhlegm rolling a double attacker down followed by a double both down on the re-roll before being taken off the pitch for a quick regen.&#xD;
&#xD;
Play continued as a full on mid-field-mess that accumulated in a foul on Acid Betty by Going for Ghould's cheeky zombie Bethany. The result: a double casualty on Acid Betty who ended up missing the rest of the game and a yellow card on Bethany who was thrown in the Dungeon, where she belongs, for the rest of the match.&#xD;
&#xD;
In all the confusion Alfred grabbed the ball and shot down field with a double going for it, only to realise that he was just short of a touchdown. This, however, had no effect on the eventual outcome that resulted in Going for Ghould's premiere touchdown.&#xD;
&#xD;
A quick restart and a few punches later saw half time in. The restart resulted in a bout of D&#xE9;j&#xE0; vu with both teams setting up in the same manner and scrumming down for the long game. After a few spritely kerfuffles, Slamgela was pushed into the crowd resulting in a Broken Jaw.&#xD;
&#xD;
The scrummage continued with Madame Ocelot jumping up with a Blitz action, rolling a 2+ for the block the smashed straight through Sour Milk's defending hand. Resident apothecaries later reported that the smashed hand would take some time to stitch back together.&#xD;
&#xD;
After some tactical blocking and follow-ups, Spleenfondler finally made a break for the end zone making a double going for it roll. Katya Cold, spotting the break from prone, jumped up, made a 50/50 dodge and proceeded to nail a double going for it and, much to to the crowds disappointment, only managed to push Spleenfondler further towards an inevitable touchdown.&#xD;
&#xD;
A restart with one turn left saw The Ru-volting Bad Drags blocking and fouling both Mummies without any notable result.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
Roll To Be Made For Fan Factor Change</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 02:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1521856855</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Sheen Scrabblers (2) vs. The Treacle Mine Pickers (1)</title>
      <description>Game 1 of the Chiswick Open was a delight for the fans.&#xD;
&#xD;
The league favourite skaven team,  The Sheen Scalrabblers faced off against the newly franchised Treacle Mine Pickers at the skaven home ground.&#xD;
&#xD;
The turn out was huge for this first game of the season, with slightly more noise in the stands for the visiting Dwarves.&#xD;
&#xD;
Conditions were bright and sunny before kick off but as the ball hit the turf for the first time the clouds came over just in time for some perfect blood bowl weather.&#xD;
&#xD;
The first half was as to be expected, the inexperienced dwarves were stretched out thinly by a well drilled skaven team, with a score delivered early in the half. This as at the cost of a number of rats who were consigned to the dugout for an early flea bath and a visit to the apothecary. After the return kick off the dwarves put in a sterling effort to deliver a touchdown in response but we're solidly pinned in their own half. The loss of their star troll slayer Carrot Ironfoundersson to a knock out was felt dearly as the skaven rat ogre smashed tirelessly through the dwarven lines.&#xD;
&#xD;
The second half saw a far more reasoned and considered approach by the dwarves, a wise offensive line up and a fortunate touchback at kick off set up a solid grind down the field. Some fast footwork and the determined efforts of the remaining troll slayer to take the rat ogre out of the game saw one of the dwarven runners sprint into the end zone for a mid half touchdown.&#xD;
&#xD;
Alas the sheer speed of the skaven was to be the dwarves undoing. During the third kickoff a stray rock from the crowd laid out the freshly revived rat ogre, giving th dwarves hope, but a blistering sprint from one of the Scrabblers sneaky gutter runners saw another touchdown on the board for the home team.&#xD;
&#xD;
At the end of time the Scrabblers had suffered a bruising 5 injuries and an outright death at the hands of the Dwarves, Carrot Ironfoundersson was the only dwarf player warming the dwarf bench, with a suspicious amount of ale tankards discarded around him...&#xD;
&#xD;
A 2-1 victory for the skaven, but a great start to the league for the dwarves, lineman Magnus Magnusson took home the dwarven award for MVP and the scorer of the second skaven touchdown took the nod there.</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1521506652</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcement by : Snake Eyes Gaming Club Open Blood Bowl League 2018</title>
      <description>Welcome to the Snake Eyes Gaming Club Open Blood Bowl League 2018.&#xD;
It allows any coach to join with any team and play any other coach/team in the league.&#xD;
&#xD;
- Starting Treasury is 1,000,000&#xD;
- A free fan factor of 5 (That does count towards team value.)&#xD;
- No Star Players&#xD;
&#xD;
To register:&#xD;
1) Click "Login" in the main menu.&#xD;
2) Click "Register" just under the login button.&#xD;
3) Fill out your Username, Email and password.&#xD;
4) Select "SEGC Open" as your League.&#xD;
5) Click "Create User"&#xD;
6) Wait for A League Commissioner to Activate your account. This will trigger an email to notify you of the activation.&#xD;
7) Login using the url provided&#xD;
8) Set your password and update your profile&#xD;
 &#xD;
&#xD;
</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1519864710</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcement by : Welcome to the SEGCBBLMS</title>
      <description>Welcome to the Snake Eyes Gaming Club Blood Bowl League Management System, SEGCBBLMS for short!</description>
      <link>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://sebbl.bigmanstudios.co.uk/index.php?1519864496</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
